INVITATION - TERUASA ODA
（邀請函，織田照朝）
Whatever danger awaits, I will crush Gungnir's ambitions.
無論前方有什麼危險 我都會摧毀永恆之槍的企圖
WOULD YOU LIKE TO ATTEND? - YES
（您想要參加嗎？是）
Yoo-hoo, Terurin.
嗨，小照照
Senya.
潛夜
You gotta be kidding me!
不會吧？
There's really no signal out here?
這裡竟然沒有訊號？
What a joke!
開什麼玩笑？
Is that Mori, the shogi Dragon King?
那是將棋的毛利龍王？
We gotta fight someone like him?
我們竟然可以對戰這樣的對手
Shit, this is gonna be intense.
不得了，比賽一定會很激烈
Welcome, my friends.
歡迎各位
I'm the organizer of this tournament.
我是這個錦標賽的籌辦人
My name is Inoru Hoshin.
我叫崩心禱
Hoshin!
崩心
No need to get carried away.
先別急
Our time will come.
我們交手的那一天總會來的
But I wonder if you'll get that far.
但你能撐到最後嗎？
You're up against some fierce opponents.
你要面對的可是強勁的對手
Here he is. Someone very important.
又來了一個人 一個非常重要的參賽者
No…
不
Why're you here?
為什麼？
Now for the real fight.
現在開始戰鬥吧
The ultimate ACMA:GAME begins.
終極ACMA:GAME開始了
Ladies and gentlemen, as chosen by the devil,
諸位都是被惡魔選中的人
each of you holds a key.
每個人都有惡魔鑰匙
Here, and all over the world,
現在，這裡和世界各地
tournament trials are underway.
已經開啟錦標賽的預選賽
The total number of keys distributed among the players is 49.
參賽者擁有的惡魔鑰匙一共有49把
In other words,
也就是說
the winner has the chance to take all 49 keys.
獲勝者有機會獲得49把惡魔鑰匙
Forty-nine?
49把？
There may also be some additional rewards for the winner.
獲勝者可能還會有額外的獎勵
Why are you doing this?
你們的目的是什麼？
You'll understand sooner or later.
到最後你就知道了
But for now,
不過現在
who wants to get their hands on all 49 keys?
誰想把49把鑰匙全部收入囊中？
I do.
我想
Me too.
我也想
I have an endless list of desires I want to fulfill.
我有一長串要實現的願望
Too bad. I'm gonna take the keys for myself.
不好意思，那些鑰匙都是我的
And you, Teruasa Oda?
織田照朝，你呢？
Suit yourself.
算了
Either way, now that you're here,
不管怎樣，你既然來到了這裡
there's no turning back.
就沒有回頭路了
Let me explain the principles of the game.
那麼我來介紹錦標賽的規則
The rules are extremely simple.
比賽規則非常簡單
The loser's life will fall into the hands of the winner.
敗者必須將生命交付給勝者
Give up our lives?
交付我們的命？
The loser's life belongs to the winner for all eternity.
敗者的性命將永遠由勝者掌控
Toying with your life until death, choosing to kill you at any moment.
到死之前 不論勝者要玩弄還是奪取性命
The loser can never defy the winner.
敗者都不能違抗
But you'll have no idea
但是，在比賽期間
what demands get made during the games, will you?
你不知道參賽者 還會提出什麼要求吧？
If you disobey the rules, there will be no additional reward.
如果不遵守規則，就得不到額外獎勵
What do you want from us?
你到底想做什麼？
We aren't your playthings.
我們不是你們的玩具
Don't you ever shut up?
請你安靜，好嗎？
I'm trying to listen to him.
我想好好聽他說話
First, we need to decide on pairs for the first round of the tournament.
現在我們需要決定 錦標賽第一輪的分組
Please choose one card.
請任意選擇一張紙牌
The person with the same mark will be your first opponent.
花色相同的人 就是第一輪中要對戰的選手
I'm first!
我先選
It's me, the idol Yukari Shikibe.
你的對手是我，偶像明星式部紫
I'm so happy to see you again.
很高興又見到你了
Nice to meet you.
請多指教
I'm a psychologist. Shunichiro Date.
我是心理學家，伊達俊一郎
Hi! I'm the famous YouTuber, Mitsuru Asai!
嗨，我是YouTube網紅，淺井滿
I'm sure you've heard of me.
你聽說過我吧？
Am I left all alone?
只有我孤單一人嗎？
Wait! This sucks.
等等，這樣多孤獨呀
Senya Uesugi, your opponent will be revealed later.
上杉潛夜先生的對手將在稍後公布
Keeping me guessing? I like your style.
要賣關子啊？有意思
First up, we have Teruasa Oda vs. Yukari Shikibe.
首先，織田照朝要對戰的是式部紫
And Ui Saito vs. Shunichiro Date.
齊藤初要對戰的是伊達俊一郎
The first round starts in one hour.
第一輪將在一個小時後開始
Will they really hand over their lives?
他們真的會賭上自己的性命嗎？
Mark my words.
一定會的
Humans are just creatures pulled by the strings of desire.
人類是無法抗拒欲望的生物
Ui.
初
What the hell happened?
這到底是怎麼回事？
I never wanted you two wrapped up in this.
我不想把你們捲進來
I've changed.
我已經不一樣了
My luck is going up.
現在我的運勢上升了
TAKEHIKO INUKAI ARRESTED FOR FRAUDULENT STOCK TRADE
（犬飼武彥因股票交易欺詐被捕）
This guy was trying to buy us out too.
這個人還想買斷我們呢
What? Really?
真的嗎？
We're lucky he was arrested.
幸虧他被逮捕，我們才能得救
Guess our luck is going up, huh?
我們的運勢在上升，悠季
Did you pick up a devil's key somewhere?
會不會是因為你撿到了惡魔鑰匙？
Stop it. You're scaring me.
不要說這種可怕的話
It was just an AI joke!
這只是一個AI玩笑啦
Your mom's been teaching me all about jokes!
最近悠季的媽媽一直在教我講笑話
Hello, this is U.U. Engineering.
您好，這裡是UU工程
Really? Our loan was approved?
我們的貸款核准了？
Thank you very much.
太感謝了
That's not all.
不僅如此
After I got the key, my true feelings were finally clear.
得到鑰匙後 我終於明白了自己的真實想法
Your true feelings?
真實想法？
Deep down, I've always wished I could fight you.
我其實早就想跟你一決高下了
What is it, Teruasa?
怎麼，照朝？
You think I can't make it through the tournament?
你覺得我沒能力在錦標賽中獲勝？
-Ui-- -I'll make sure I win.
-初… -我一定會贏的
Then I'll take you on next.
接著再跟你對戰
Now leave me alone.
別管我的事了
The first round is about to begin.
第一輪比賽即將開始
Players are asked…
參賽者…
Terurin!
小照照
…to move to the game room.
…請到遊戲室集合
If you lose before you get to me,
如果你在對上我之前輸了
I'll never forgive you.
我永遠都不會原諒你
Well, go get 'em.
好了，加油
I'm gonna get in the zone by checking out the area.
我也要打起精神，好好調查這個地方
ARENA ONE
（第一會場）
I'm going to fight with all I've got.
我會竭盡全力跟你對戰的
ARENA TWO
（第二會場）
Let the ACMA:GAME tournament
ACMA:GAME錦標賽
commence.
要開始了
So, we meet again,
我們又見面了
Teruasa Oda, Yukari Shikibe.
織田照朝，式部紫
Gado! You're in a good mood.
卡多，你心情不錯嘛
That's because you humans invent such cruel yet delightful games.
這是因為你們人類 想出了如此殘酷又令人愉悅的遊戲
An ACMA:GAME tournament.
也就是ACMA:GAME錦標賽
Let's get started straightaway.
我們馬上開始吧
I have a question first.
我想先問你一個問題
A question?
問題？
Ui found a devil's key.
初得到了一把惡魔鑰匙
Who dropped it?
是誰給他的？
I'll explain.
那我就告訴你吧
The one who let a devil's key fall at Ui Saito's feet
讓惡魔鑰匙掉落在齊藤初面前的
was me.
是我
Why would you do that?
你為什麼要這麼做？
Watching humans suffer at the mercy of their desires
看著人類被欲望擺佈
is a devil's greatest pleasure.
對惡魔來說，是一種無與倫比的快樂
Are you devils
你們這些惡魔
being manipulated by Gungnir?
會不會是被永恆之槍利用了？
Time to start the game.
要開始遊戲了
What do you want to bet?
你們想賭什麼？
The loser will give his life
敗者要將自己的性命
to the winner.
交付給勝者
Same here.
我也一樣
I'm gonna be on the edge of my seat to the very end.
我會愉快地看到最後的
Now take your oaths.
那麼宣誓吧
I will fight for my desires.
我會為我的欲望而戰
I will triumph for my desires.
我會為我的欲望奪勝
-I swear on the devil.
-我向惡魔宣誓
Oaths accepted.
我接受你們的宣誓
Let the game begin!
遊戲開始
"Hide &amp; See."
“隱蔽看破”
Now for the rules.
我來解釋規則
One player is a Hider and the other is a Seer.
首先，玩家分為隱藏者和看破者
The Seer must sit in the chair on stage.
看破者要坐在臺上的椅子上面
The Seer cannot leave the seat until he or she gives an answer.
看破者在給出答案之前 不能從椅子上站起來
The Hider takes this coin
隱藏者要拿著硬幣
and hides it somewhere in the designated arena.
並把它藏在封閉空間的某個地方
Once hidden, the Hider says, "I'm ready."
藏好之後，隱藏者要說：“我藏好了”
Basically, the Seer has to find where the Hider has hidden the coin?
也就是說，看破者 要找出隱藏者把硬幣藏在哪裡
Exactly.
沒錯
However, you don't need to give specific details as to where the coin is.
不過 看破者不必詳細說出硬幣的位置
The Seer must simply declare which of the six tables
只需要說出隱藏的硬幣
is closest to the hidden coin.
離六張桌子中的哪一張最近
1 TABLE - 100 POINTS 2 TABLES - 50 POINTS
（1張：100分，2張：50分）
3 TABLES - 30 POINTS
（3張：30分）
You may choose several tables if you wish.
選擇的桌數可以是一至五桌
4 TABLES - 20 POINTS 5 TABLES - 10 POINTS
（4桌：20分，5桌：10分）
Naturally, the fewer tables you choose, the higher the score for a correct answer.
當然，選擇的桌數越少 答對時得到的分數越高
You switch roles each turn, with three sets in total.
每局遊戲互換一次角色，一共比三局
What happens if the coin changes position
如果看破者在分析應該選哪張桌子時
while the Seer is wondering which table to choose?
硬幣的位置變了怎麼辦？
What if it falls, or rolls somewhere else after you've hidden it?
硬幣在藏好後掉落了或滾到別的地方 會怎麼評判？
The coin location is decided
硬幣的位置為
once the Hider says, "I'm ready."
隱藏者宣布“我藏好了”時的位置
It makes no difference if it moves after that.
在這之後，即使它移動了也沒關係
Got it.
我知道了
Yukari Shikibe used her devil's key,
式部紫使用了她的惡魔鑰匙
which means she gets a devil power.
也就是說，她可以使用惡魔之力
We'll toss a coin.
現在拋硬幣
What will it be? Heads or tails?
玩家選擇正面或背面
-Heads. -Tails.
-正面 -背面
Teruasa Oda, which role do you choose first?
織田照朝，你想先當什麼角色？
I'll be the Seer.
看破者
I bet she wanted Seer first too.
我猜她也想先當看破者這個角色
Now I can see what the arena looks like from the stage, and check for blind spots.
現在我可以在臺上觀察遊戲場地 然後找出視覺盲區
With that, Hide &amp; See begins!
“隱蔽看破”遊戲現在開始
Crap, no signal.
該死，沒訊號
Come on.
快點
Come on, signal.
來點訊號
Who are you again?
我忘了，你是誰？
Famous YouTuber Asai!
YouTube網紅，淺井
We literally just met!
我們剛剛不是才見過面嗎？
Hey!
喂
SET ONE - HEADS
（第一局，正面）
The first Hider is Yukari Shikibe.
先當隱藏者的是式部紫
Hide the coin.
請隱藏硬幣
There are more blind spots than I thought.
視覺盲區比我想的要多
I need to keep my eyes peeled for any unnatural movements.
我要觀察她不自然的動作 一瞬間也不能錯過
Is she trying to make it look like she's hidden it at every table?
她假裝在每一張桌子上藏硬幣？
That's a solid approach.
這是有效的策略
I'm going to have to rely on a luck alone.
如果是這樣，我只能憑運氣來回答了
If I choose five tables,
即使我選五張桌子
there's still a one-in-six, 17% chance I'll be wrong.
猜錯的機率還是有六分之一 也就是17%
Even if I win, I'll only get ten points.
就算我猜對了，也只能得10分
I'm ready.
我藏好了
Teruasa Oda, as the Seer,
看破者織田照朝
you must choose the closest table to the hidden coin.
你要說出離硬幣最近的桌子
Since she didn't go near table six,
既然式部紫沒有靠近六號桌
it makes sense to choose from tables one to five.
照理講我應該選一至五號桌
But why didn't she go near table six?
但她為什麼沒有靠近六號桌？
That's the only strange thing she did.
這是她唯一不自然的地方
Wait…
等等
There it is.
我知道了
An unnatural movement.
不自然的動作
Can you get on with it?
可以快一點嗎？
How much time do you need to think?
你還要考慮多久？
Sorry.
不好意思
But I wasn't thinking.
不過，我不是在考慮
I was observing.
我是在觀察
Come again?
什麼？
Yukari Shikibe,
式部紫
while you were waiting, I was watching for unnatural movements.
在等待時，我在偷偷觀察妳
You didn't notice me looking.
是否有不自然的動作
Your gaze shifted in many directions.
妳的視線朝很多個方向移動
But you didn't look at table six once.
但是妳唯獨堅決不看六號桌
Humans tend to subconsciously avert their gaze from something they're hiding.
人會無意識地 將視線從想要隱藏的事物上移開
In other words, table six, the one you wouldn't look at,
也就是說，妳眼神迴避的六號桌
is exactly where I should look.
有不想被我發現的東西
Stop blurting random crap.
你別亂說
I didn't even go near table six.
我根本沒靠近六號桌
How could I have put the coin there?
怎麼把硬幣藏到那裡？
What if you rolled it from behind table five?
如果妳從五號桌後面 將硬幣滾過去呢？
There's a blind spot, so I wouldn't have seen you do it.
那裡有一個我看不見的盲區
Teruasa Oda, what is your answer?
織田照朝，說出你的答案
I choose table six.
我選六號桌
Table six.
六號桌
Incorrect.
錯誤
The correct answer is table four.
正確答案是四號桌
I knew you were "observing" me from the very start.
我從一開始就知道你在觀察我
When people are watching,
當別人在看著我時
I never stop paying attention to how I look.
我隨時都有意識地展現出特定的一面
That's idol life.
當偶像就是這樣的
There's seriously no signal at all.
這裡完全沒訊號
Not a soul in sight either.
一個人影也沒有
Gives me the creeps.
感覺好詭異
The creeps?
詭異？
Mog chocolate? Gimme.
莫格巧克力？給我一塊
Hands off. My friend gave this to me.
不行，這是我朋友送我的
-So what? -Hey.
-那又怎麼樣？ -喂
Don't hog it all.
不要那麼小氣
Okay, fine! Sorry.
好啦，不好意思，對不起
SET ONE - TAILS
（第一局，背面）
Next, the Hider is Teruasa Oda.
接下來當隱藏者的是織田照朝
Hide the coin.
請隱藏硬幣
Why's he checking the curtains and pillars?
他為什麼要檢查窗簾和柱子？
Is he going to hide it there?
他要藏在那裡嗎？
What now?
這是幹什麼？
What's he up to?
他要做什麼？
He still hasn't hidden it?
他還沒藏嗎？
I'm ready.
我藏好了
That's gotta be table four, right?
不管怎麼看，都應該選四號桌
Gado, are the table numbers fixed at the start?
卡多，桌號是一開始就固定的嗎？
Or do they change if you move the number plates?
還是根據號碼牌的位置而改變？
The current number plates are valid.
可以按現在的號碼牌來回答
What a shame.
可惜了
Your plan wasn't just to move the tables.
你的目的不是移動桌子
You wanted to switch the number plates,
而是更換號碼牌
to make table five appear to be table four.
把原來的五號桌變成現在的四號桌
But you heard him. I can use the current number plates.
但是你聽到了 我可以按現在的號碼牌來回答
That was a little clumsy.
你這一招真草率
I choose table four.
我選四號桌
Table four.
四號桌
Incorrect.
錯誤
The correct answer is table one.
正確答案是一號桌
Are you kidding me?
你說什麼？
It's right here!
硬幣就在這裡
It's…
這個…
a fake?
是假幣？
Was this your plan from the beginning?
你從一開始就準備了這個？
You misled me into thinking I'd discovered your number plate plan.
然後你還故意 讓我識破了你換號碼牌的把戲
You tricked me?
以此誤導我？
He's good at this after all.
織田照朝果然很厲害
I'm starving.
好餓啊
This is exhausting.
累死人了
Can we go now?
可以走了嗎？
A radio tower?
電波塔？
What? You mean there's signal?
什麼？電波？
Shit.
糟糕
Shit, shit, shit!
完蛋了
It's coming!
它來了
What the heck was that?
那是什麼？
A self-destructing drone.
自爆式無人機
Looks like we were the targets.
好像是衝著我們來的
You can't be serious.
不會吧？
Those guys aren't messing around.
難道那些傢伙…
They really want us dead.
真的想殺了我們？
Neither of you scored points, so the first set is a tie.
在第一局中 兩人均未得分，所以打成平局
Fingers crossed for more treachery in the second set.
期待下一局有更多詐人的花招
You're very good at this.
你確實厲害
But there's someone I'm even more scared of playing.
但是在比賽中 有一個我更不想遇到的對手
The psychologist Shunichiro Date.
就是那個心理學家，伊達俊一郎
The first set's score is 20-0.
第一局的比分是20比0
Shunichiro Date wins.
伊達俊一郎勝出
He can read people completely.
他可以輕易讀懂人的心思
No one can beat him.
誰都贏不了他
That's just the beginning.
不僅如此
He is cruel.
他還非常冷酷
To him, people are just research subjects.
對他而言，人類只不過是研究對象
If you put your life in his hands, who knows what horrible things he'll do.
如果把性命交給他 會發生什麼可怕的事情？
You must be worried.
你一定很擔心
His opponent is a dear friend of yours.
伊達的對手是你的好朋友吧？
I wonder how he must be suffering.
他現在有多痛苦呢？
Is it painful to imagine?
光用想的就很難受，對吧？
But wait.
不過
Didn't you guys have an argument?
你們剛才鬧得不愉快吧？
Perhaps it's kinda convenient then!
這反而讓你減輕負擔了
You're a malicious creature.
真是個無情的女人
My favorite.
我喜歡
SET TWO - HEADS
（第二局，正面）
The Hider is Yukari Shikibe.
隱藏者是式部紫
Hide the coin.
請隱藏硬幣
I'm ready.
我藏好了
Well, Teruasa Oda,
那麼織田照朝
which table do you choose?
請選擇桌子
What was she doing?
怎麼回事？
She didn't go near tables one, two or three.
她沒靠近一、二或三號桌
Then at first glance,
從表面上看
if I guess tables four, five and six, I'll win thirty points.
如果選四、五和六號桌，我能得30分
But is that really it?
但是，真的可以這麼選嗎？
Why would she risk not going near three tables?
她為什麼冒險不靠近那三張桌子？
Perhaps…
難道…
I used a devil power?
我使用惡魔之力了嗎？
That's what you're thinking.
你在想這個問題吧？
I'm sorry if my words upset you earlier.
很抱歉之前說了讓你難過的話
I'll give you a hint to make up for it.
我給你一個提示，以示歉意
My devil power is called
我的惡魔之力
Double Invisible.
叫“隱形分身”
Invisible?
分身？
Transparency?
透明？
She can create a double of herself that I can't see?
難道她能創造我看不見的分身？
Was she moving weirdly
她做出不自然的動作
because she was controlling her double?
是因為要控制她的分身嗎？
Was that why her gaze was out of focus
她摔倒時眼神空洞
when she fell down?
也是因為分身嗎？
Then where did her real self hide the coin?
如果是這樣，她的透明分身 把硬幣藏到了哪裡？
Table one, two, or three?
一、二或三號桌？
But the whole thing could be an act.
但是，這一切有可能是她演的
Which is it?
要怎麼選？
Teruasa Oda,
那麼，織田照朝
make your choice.
做出你的選擇
I choose tables one, two and three.
我選擇一、二和三號桌
Incorrect.
錯誤
The correct answer is table four.
正確答案是四號桌
This time you put on an act, only pretending to use your devil power.
這一次妳演了一齣戲 假裝使用了惡魔之力
I love people like you who are easy to trick.
像你這麼好騙的人，我太喜歡了
Idols trick their fans for a living.
偶像的工作就是演戲給粉絲看
Well, well. Let's continue the game.
好，遊戲繼續
SET TWO - TAILS
（第二局，背面）
At this rate, she's going to win.
照這樣下去，她就贏定了
I need to take back control.
我要奪回掌控權
Awaken the devil power.
喚醒惡魔之力
LIMITED PERFECT
（有限完美）
I'm ready.
我藏好了
Shit, I missed it.
糟了，我錯過了
Yukari Shikibe, you are the Seer.
看破者是式部紫
Choose your table.
請選擇桌子
I can't panic now.
我現在不能慌
That's exactly what he wants.
這樣正合他意
It's fine. I can do this.
沒關係，我一定會贏的
As it stands, my best bet is to choose four tables and secure 20 points.
按現在來看 我最好是選四張桌子，拿20分
Then he'll be under pressure in the third set.
這樣到第三局，他就會倍感壓力
The problem is which tables to choose.
問題是，我應該選哪四張桌子
I have a devil's key,
我有惡魔鑰匙
so I should be lucky…
這樣應該會得到好運
Three.
三
Four.
四
One.
一
Five.
五
Yukari Shikibe, time to answer.
式部紫，說出妳的答案
I choose table one, three, four and five.
我選擇一、三、四、五號桌
Correct.
正確
Yukari Shikibe,
式部紫
since you chose four tables, you gain 20 points.
妳選擇了四張桌子，因此得20分
At the end of the second set,
在第二局中
Yukari Shikibe is in the lead at 20-0.
式部紫以20比0獲勝
You are totally cornered,
你被逼到絕境了
Teruasa Oda.
織田照朝
At the end of the second set, the score is 30-30.
第二局的比分是30比30
A tie.
雙方打平
He's more clever and decisive than expected.
他比我想的還要聰明和果斷
Above all, his unwavering determination to win is formidable.
最重要的是，他的奪勝決心非常驚人
I wonder…
那麼…
What kind of experiment shall I use him for?
我該用他來做什麼實驗呢？
Then now it is time for the third and final set.
現在開始第三局，也是最後一局
Teruasa Oda, your turn to get on stage.
看破者織田照朝，請到臺上
Yukari Shikibe,
式部紫
I've figured you out.
我已經看穿妳了
It's my turn to win.
不好意思，輪到我贏了
The third set of Hide &amp; See begins.
“隱蔽看破”的第三局開始
SET THREE - HEADS
（第三局，正面）
Why would Teruasa Oda say that?
織田照朝為什麼說那些話？
Was he just lashing out because I'm winning?
因為我領先了，所以他要洩憤？
Why's he not watching?
他為什麼不看我？
He should have his eyes glued to me at a time like this.
他應該在這種時候 目不轉睛地盯著我才對
What's wrong?
怎麼了？
Haven't you hidden it yet?
還不開始藏硬幣嗎？
How did he know I haven't hidden it yet?
他怎麼知道我還沒藏起來？
I can't miss a thing.
我不能放過任何小細節
I have to beat him.
織田照朝
I've got to.
我一定要打敗他
His phone?
手機？
There's no signal here.
這個封閉空間裡沒訊號
What's he looking at?
他在看什麼？
No way. There's a camera.
難道…攝影機
Was he trying to connect to the camera when he was touching the curtain?
他每次摸窗簾，是為了靠近攝影機 讓手機連線嗎？
Is he really capable of that?
他真的能連上嗎？
I wouldn't put it past him after he used that phony coin.
不過他既然能想到用假幣 讓手機連線也就不奇怪了
What do I do?
該怎麼辦？
Find a blind spot that's also hidden from the camera?
找一個織田照朝和攝影機 都看不到的盲區？
No.
不
Instead, I'll use it against you.
我要以其人之道，還治其人之身
I'm ready.
我藏好了
The Seer is Teruasa Oda.
看破者織田照朝
Choose your table.
請選擇桌子
Teruasa Oda,
織田照朝
I already have you in my trap.
你中了我的圈套
If you're not monitoring the camera,
如果不藉助攝影機的監視
you need to choose between tables one to six
你只能憑運氣
purely on the basis of luck.
在一號桌到六號桌之間做選擇
And if you are monitoring the camera,
如果藉助攝影機的監視
you'd have seen me hiding the coin at table four.
你會看到我把硬幣藏在四號桌
But what you don't know is that it's the fake coin you used earlier.
但你不知道的是 那是你之前用過的假幣
Either way, you can't win.
不管怎麼樣，你都贏不了
Teruasa Oda, time for your answer.
織田照朝，請回答
I choose table five.
我選擇五號桌
Correct.
正確
Shit.
怎麼會？
I noticed you holding the fake coin.
我知道妳拿著假幣
So I misled you into using it.
所以我才誘導妳使用它
I knew it.
我猜到了
I knew you'd be sharp enough
像妳這麼厲害的人
to suspect I was watching the camera,
會懷疑我在看監視畫面
and then use it to your advantage.
然後將此作為自己的優勢
I'm not a bad actor either.
我的演技也不差
Teruasa Oda,
織田照朝
since you chose one table, you win 100 points.
你選擇了一張桌子，因此獲得100分
It's not over yet.
還沒結束
I still get one turn to be Seer.
我還能當一次看破者
The last turn.
終於到最後一回合了
Keep up the entertaining work.
讓我看個過癮吧
I'm gambling everything on this game.
我把一切都押在這個遊戲上了
I need to concentrate, so keep quiet.
我要集中注意力，所以請保持安靜
Especially you and your loud voice.
特別是你的大嗓門
It hurts my ears.
很刺耳
Hurts your ears?
刺耳？
I really wanna win this.
我一定要贏
So don't distract me.
所以不要讓我分心
Only because the game is heating up,
看在遊戲越來越刺激的份上
you can have it your way.
我就忍忍吧
Please, let me win.
拜託，讓我贏吧
Praying to the devil in times of distress, huh?
在困難的時候向惡魔祈禱？
Begin!
遊戲開始
SET THREE - TAILS
（第三局，背面）
He's doing the same thing at each table.
他在所有桌子上都做同樣的動作
The best way to make it difficult.
這是增加難度最好的辦法
I'm ready.
我藏好了
Now Yukari Shikibe, as the Seer,
看破者式部紫
choose your table.
請選擇桌子
But I'm going to win this.
但是，我一定能贏
Just watch me take 100 points.
我一定能得100分
She's taking longer than usual.
她竟然要思考這麼久
This is the last chance.
這是最後的機會
It makes sense to be extra careful.
她慎重一些也是理所當然
But…
但是…
her expression.
她的表情
What does it mean?
是什麼意思？
She's waiting for something, quietly confident.
她在信心滿滿地等著什麼
Is she acting again?
這也是在演戲嗎？
No. There's no point acting when she's the one searching for the coin.
不，現在她是尋找硬幣的人 沒必要演戲
What's she waiting for?
她在等什麼？
Could this be
難道
her real devil power?
這才是她真正的惡魔之力？
Then where is her real body?
這個能力是什麼呢？
I need to concentrate, so keep quiet.
我要集中注意力，所以請保持安靜
Especially you and your loud voice.
特別是你的大嗓門
It hurts my ears.
很刺耳
That's it.
對了
All Timer?
萬物計時器？
That's right.
沒錯
Focus your attention on an object of your choice,
對你選擇的事物集中注意力
and it will make a noise for 30 seconds.
它會發出30秒的聲響
That's my devil power?
這就是我的惡魔之力
But it won't kick in until ten minutes after the power is unleashed.
但是它需要在惡魔之力 啟動十分鐘後才生效
Isn't it just perfect for this game?
這能力是不是很適合這個遊戲？
Ten minutes?
十分鐘？
Please, let me win.
拜託，讓我贏吧
ALL TIMER
（萬物計時器）
Now I can't hear the timer.
我聽不到計時器的聲音
Where is it?
它在哪裡？
Just as I thought, a power that uses sound to reveal location.
果然如我所料 這是通過聲音來確定位置的限時能力
I've always been alone.
我一直孤獨一人
Abandoned at an orphanage as soon as I was born.
一出生就被遺棄在孤兒院
I've lived my whole life without letting anyone in.
這輩子我從未對任何人打開心房
But I've always wanted to be seen.
但是我一直想要得到別人的關注
YOU BECAME AN IDOL AND EVERYONE LOVES YOU
（你當上偶像明星了 大家都喜歡你）
That's why I wanted to be an idol.
因此我當上了偶像明星
I dreamt of being loved all over the world.
我夢想著能得到全世界的愛
Yukari Shikibe, what is your answer?
式部紫，請說出妳的答案
My choice is…
我的選擇是
table one.
一號桌
Incorrect.
錯誤
The correct answer was table six.
正確答案是六號桌
The final score is 100-20.
最終的比分是100比20
The winner of Hide &amp; See is Teruasa Oda!
因此“隱蔽看破”的勝者是織田照朝
Teruasa Oda,
織田照朝
from now on, Yukari Shikibe's life is yours.
從現在開始，式部紫的生命歸你掌控
I look forward to seeing what you do with her life.
你會怎麼操控她的生命？我拭目以待
Why?
為什麼？
Why did I have to lose?
我為什麼會輸？
The flames of desire ignite conflict.
欲望的火焰會點燃衝突
Try to become someone who can save those
你試著成為一個拯救者吧
who become consumed by desire.
拯救被欲望吞噬的人
Yukari Shikibe,
式部紫
you're a tough player.
妳很了不起
You should have trusted your own strength instead of relying on luck.
妳應該相信自己的實力 而不是依賴運氣
The power to win was already in you.
妳自己已經擁有獲勝的能力
Teruasa Oda…
織田照朝
I hate your guts.
我恨死你了
Now for the results of Hide &amp; See.
現在宣布“隱蔽看破”的結果
The final score is 80-50.
最終比分是80比50
Ui Saito wins!
齊藤初獲勝
It's an honor to entrust my life
能把我的生命
to someone of such caliber.
交付給你這麼優秀的人，我很榮幸
Teruasa Oda managed to win.
織田照朝贏了
He's very strong-willed.
他很有骨氣
I see why The Guide had high expectations.
難怪引領者大人對他期望甚高
But,
不過
let's see what happens in the second round.
第二輪的結果會怎麼樣呢？
Ui!
初
Who won?
比賽結果如何？
You're my next opponent.
我的下一個對手是你
The next game will be a tough one for Teruasa Oda.
下一場比賽對織田照朝來說非常殘酷
Is it time yet?
還不開始嗎？
I can't wait for a fight. The anticipation is killing me!
真想趕快戰鬥，我興奮到快受不了了
What happened? You guys look miserable.
小紫，妳怎麼了？怎麼愁眉苦臉的？
What a roller coaster that was yesterday.
昨天的比賽很激烈
Today, another game begins.
今天新的比賽要開始了
The genius shogi player, Akira Mori,
天才棋士毛利明
will face famous YouTuber Mitsuru Asai in a special show down.
將會與YouTube網紅淺井滿 展開一場特別的對決
I have high expectations.
我好期待
Hey, who am I playing?
那我的對手呢？
I'm sick of waiting.
我不想再等了
Yes, yes.
我知道
You opponent has just arrived.
那就請你的對手出場吧
Yuki?
悠季？
Senya Uesugi's opponent is Yuki Manabe.
上杉潛夜的對手是真鍋悠季
Show us a good game, okay?
讓我們欣賞一場有趣的對決吧
NEXT EPISODE
（下集預告）
What do you want us for?
你到底為何叫我們來？
"Gold Gun &amp; Silver Gun."
“金槍和銀槍”
The person who shoots first wins the money.
先開槍的人能贏得獎金
To shoot or not to shoot.
要開槍還是不開槍
YUKI VS SENYA
（悠季對潛夜）
There's only one thing she can do. Win the game.
她能做的只有一件事 那就是贏得比賽
Jump!
快跳